{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        },
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        },
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        },
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        },
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        },
        {
            "Question": "True of false: A donkey is able to see all four of its feet?",
            "Answers": [ "True", "False" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "True"
        },
        {
            "Question": "A group of crows are referred to as a what?",
            "Answers": [ "I wont tell you", "A group of crows", "A something of crows", "A murder of crows" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "A murder of crows"
        },
        {
            "Question": "What sea creature is a blue whale's favourite meal?",
            "Answers": [ "Dunno", "Really dont know", "Krill", "Uhhhh" ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Krill"
        }
    ]
}